tecademics.com 2017-09-21

# - Tecademics - The School for Internet Marketers

Tecademics (referred to herein as “Tecademics,” “our,” “us” or “we”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of those visiting our websites, including our independent contractors’ Replicated Websites (hereafter collectively referred to as the “Website” or “Websites”). Tecademics created this Privacy Policy to give you confidence as you visit and use the Websites, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy.

We recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. The purpose of this policy is to let you know how we handle the information collected through the use of this website. Portions of this website may describe privacy practices applicable to specific types of information or to information provided on specific web pages.

This policy does not apply to information collected through other means such as by telephone or in person, although that information may be protected by other privacy policies. As used in this policy, terms such as “we” or “our” and “Company” refer to Tecademics and its current and future affiliated entities.

This website is intended for a United States audience. Any information you provide, including any personal information, will be transferred to and processed by a computer server located within the United States.

This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Websites and not to any Third-Party websites, which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below.

**BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.**

Each time you use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time you use the Website you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time you visited the Website. For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to the Privacy Policy, below.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY; INFORMATION FOR CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13.** Tecademics will not intentionally collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 through this website without receiving parental consent. If you think that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 through this website, please contact us. Tecademics has designed this Privacy Policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Policy Act (COPPA). 

Portions of this website may describe privacy practices applicable to specific types of information or to information provided on specific web pages. This policy does not apply to information collected through 08.11.2016 Tecademics Privacy Policy Page 2 other means such as by telephone or in person, although that information may be protected by other privacy policies.

Tecademics does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Tecademics obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, Tecademics will immediately delete such information from its database. Because Tecademics does not knowingly or intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, Tecademics has no such information to use or disclose to third parties.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

Tecademics is the sole owner of the Website, including the Replicated Websites. We collect information from independent contractors, customers, and visitors to the Websites at different points on the Websites.

**TRAFFIC DATA**

Tecademics automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of devices accessing the Website; and (iv) types of web browsers accessing the Website (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you.

**COOKIES AND TRAFFIC DATA**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website. The purpose of a cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the website. Tecademics uses cookies to customize your experience on the Website to your interests, to ensure that you do not see the same informational messages repeatedly, and to store your username so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Website. For additional information on Tecademics’ uses of cookies, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies, below.

The Company uses various technologies, which may include “cookie” technology, to gather information from our visitors such as pages visited and how often they are visited, and to enable certain features on this website. “Cookies” are small text files that may be placed on your computer when you visit a website or click on a URL. Cookies may include “single-session cookies” which generally record information during only a single visit to a website and then are erased, and “persistent” cookies which are generally stored on a computer unless or until they are deleted or are set to expire.

You may disable cookies and similar items by adjusting your browser preferences at any time; however, this may limit your ability to take advantage of all the features on this website.

We may also allow third party service providers to use cookies and other technologies to collect information and to track browsing activity over time and across third party websites such as web browsers used to read our websites, which websites are referring traffic or linking to our websites, and to deliver targeted advertisements to you. We do not control these third party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies.

We may use analytics companies to gather information and aggregate data from our website visitors such as which pages are visited and how often they are visited, and to enable certain features on our websites. Information is captured using various technologies and may include cookies. We may use and disclose your activity information unless restricted by this policy or by law. Some examples of the ways we use your activity information include:

  * Customizing your experience on the website including managing and recording your preferences.
  * Marketing, product development, and research purposes.
  * Tracking resources and data accessed on the website.
  * Developing reports regarding website usage, activity, and statistics.
  * Assisting users experiencing website problems.
  * Enabling certain functions and tools on this website.
  * Tracking paths of visitors to this website and within this website.

**IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN OF THE SERVICES AND CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.**

**YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

This Website may include web pages that give you the opportunity to provide us with personal information about yourself. You do not have to provide us with personal information if you do not want to; however, that may limit your ability to use certain functions of this Website or to request certain services or information. Personal Information that is collected from customers, independent contractors and registered customers through Customer Registration, Product or Services Purchases, and/or Surveys is used and disclosed as described in this Privacy Policy. Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, Tecademics DOES NOT share personal information. Tecademics may share aggregated information from time to time with its partners, vendors or other third parties. When such aggregate information is shared by Tecademics, no personal information is shared. We may use personal information for a number of purposes such as:

  * To respond to an email or particular request from you.
  * To personalize the website for you.
  * To process an application as requested by you.
  * To administer surveys and promotions.
  * To provide you with information that we believe may be useful to you, such as information about health products or services provided by us or other businesses.
  * To perform analytics and to improve our products, websites, and advertising.
  * To comply with applicable laws, regulations, and legal process.
  * To protect someone’s health, safety, or welfare. 08.11.2016 Tecademics Privacy Policy Page 4
  * To protect our rights, the rights of affiliates or related third parties, or take appropriate legal action, such as to enforce our Terms of Use.
  * To keep a record of our transactions and communications.
  * As otherwise necessary or useful for us to conduct our business, so long as such use is permitted by law.

We may supplement the personal information you provide with additional personal information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide such information to Tecademics. You are under no obligation to provide personal information, with the caveat that your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain of the features and services available on the Website or from purchasing any of our products.

**INDEPENDENT CONTRACTORS AND CUSTOMER REGISTRATION**

In order to become an independent contractor, an applicant must provide certain personal information to us. We also may require an applicant’s Social Security Number or Federal Tax ID Number so that we may prepare and file necessary non-employee compensation forms for the IRS. Certain customers may be required to register in order to purchase products directly from us. Registered customers will be required to provide personal information. We use this information to maintain contact with independent contractors and registered customers, and to process independent contractor and registered customer orders.

**PRODUCT OR SERVICE PURCHASES**

When a customer, registered customer, or independent contractor purchases products or services from us through any of our websites, the purchaser must provide us with certain personal information. This information is used for billing and payment purposes and to fill orders.

**INFORMATION THAT YOU MAKE PUBLIC**

The Website may contains features (e.g., public profiles, forums, and message boards) that permit you to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, information or other material, including some of your personal information. Any information that you choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information over which Tecademics is unable to exercise any control. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information by any means and you agree to assume all responsibility for doing so.

**INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES**

Tecademics analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using cookies to help Tecademics better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Tecademics is able to better design the Website to improve your experience, and to serve you more relevant and interesting content. From time to time, Tecademics may release Traffic Data and information gathered using cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. Tecademics does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to personal information.

**SHARING INFORMATION**

Except under the following circumstances and otherwise as set forth in this Privacy Policy, Tecademics will only share your personal information with third parties as outlined in this policy and as otherwise permitted by law.

We may share personal information if all or part of the Company is sold, merged, dissolved, acquired, or in a similar transaction.

We may share personal information in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law or regulation. We may cooperate with law enforcement authorities in investigating and prosecuting activities that are illegal, violate our rules, or may be harmful to other visitors.

If you submit information or a posting to a chat room, bulletin board, or similar “chat” related portion of this Website, the information you submit along with your screen name will be visible to all visitors, and such visitors may share with others. Therefore, please be thoughtful in what you write and understand that this information may become public.

We may also share personal information with other third party companies that we collaborate with or hire to perform services on our behalf. For example, we may hire a company to help us send and manage email, and we might provide the company with your email address and certain other information in order for them to send you an email message on our behalf. Similarly, we may hire companies to host or operate some of our Websites and related computers and software applications.

Tecademics discloses personal information to those who help it provide services, including those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security, when required by law or to protect rights. Tecademics discloses personal information in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Tecademics believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Tecademics.

When legally required by law enforcement, judicial and administrative agency disclosures, Tecademics will provide confidential and personally identifiable information as necessary to comply with judicial and administrative orders, subpoenas, civil or criminal investigative demands, administrative and regulatory demands and other legal obligations. In order for Tecademics to conduct business in certain jurisdictions, Tecademics must disclose certain personally identifiable and confidential information to regulatory authorities in such jurisdictions. Such information may include, but is not limited to, income information and personally identifiable information.

Tecademics reserves the right to transfer all personal information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Tecademics’ assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred personal information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it.

Personal information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by Tecademics’ successor organization, if any.

If you have failed to pay any balance owed in consideration of products or services, Tecademics may, as permitted by law, report your personal information, including without limitation, your unpaid balance, to consumer credit reporting services, collection agencies and others.

Tecademics occasionally may assign prospective sales and new independent contractors leads to independent contractors. In these cases, Tecademics will provide the lead with the appropriate independent contractors name and contact information. In addition, Tecademics may have an Independent Contractor Locator feature on its Website. Pursuant to this feature, a prospective customer or new independent contractor can locate a nearby Tecademics independent contractor. In order to make the Independent Contractor Locator feature and the lead assignments effective, the Company will provide the prospective customer or new independent contractor with the independent contractor’s name and contact information, which may include his/her telephone number, address, and/or email address.

To help independent contractors in Tecademics’ affiliate marketing program manage their independent businesses, we may provide your sponsor and other up-line independent contractors with your name, address, telephone number, and email address, as well as data relating to your sales and recruitment activity through the back office to the Website.

**COMMUNICATIONS FROM US**

When enrolling as an independent contractor, registering as registered customer, or making a purchase or other inquiry through the Website, you consent to receive periodic email and other communications from us and from Tecademics independent contractors. For example, Tecademics sends all new independent contractors and registered customers a welcoming email to verify password, username, and acceptance of the Independent Contractor’s Agreement or Customer Agreement. All independent contractors and registered customers will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Customers who have not registered with Tecademics and who grant permission will also receive occasional information on products, services, special deals, and the like.

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send independent contractors or customers an email. Generally, independent contractors may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their accounts. These communications are not promotional in nature.

Tecademics communicates with independent contractors and registered customers via email, regular mail and telephone on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their Tecademics business. Tecademics communicates with other customers with respect to products or services purchased by such customers from Tecademics. Such communications may be by email, regular mail or telephone.

**LINKS**

Tecademics Websites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Tecademics is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Tecademics Websites.

**SECURITY**

Tecademics has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of your personal information.

**LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION**

You must promptly notify us if your credit, banking, other financial information, user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number, bank account information, other financial institution information, user name or password from your account.

**PROMOTIONAL ACTIVITIES**

From time to time, Tecademics may conduct contests, giveaways and other promotions (collectively, “Promotional Activities”). Any information submitted in connection with Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, Tecademics may also ask you to participate in surveys designed to help Tecademics improve the Websites, its products, services, or the Tecademics affiliate marketing program. Any personal information provided to Tecademics in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Tecademics reserves the right to amend or change this Privacy Policy at any time at its sole discretion. It is your responsibility to periodically access this Privacy Policy by clicking on the Privacy Policy link at our Website. You can determine the date this Privacy Policy was last updated by referring to the effective date found at the end of the policy. When material changes or amendments are made to the Privacy Policy, we will announce the same at our home page for a period of 3 days following implementation of the amended Privacy Policy.

**MAKING CHANGES TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Independent contractors and registered Customers may update their personal information as necessary by logging into their Tecademics online Back Offices, which allows them to access and edit their registration account information. In addition, Independent Contractors and Registered Customers may contact us at askmeanything@tecademics.com.

**SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER PROTECTION POLICY**

Protecting personal information is important to Tecademics. It is our policy to protect the confidentiality of Social Security numbers (“SSNs”) that we receive or collect in the course of business. We secure the confidentiality of SSNs through various means, including physical, technical, and administrative safeguards that are designed to protect against unauthorized access. It is our policy to limit access to SSNs to that which is lawful, and to prohibit unlawful disclosure of SSNs.

**SOCIAL MEDIA DISCLAIMER**

We are under no obligation to screen or monitor your posts or any other User Content; however, we may make a reasonable effort to monitor participation to ensure that you stay on topic, are courteous and avoid making offensive comments. Your posts and User content must adhere to the following requirements and cannot:

  * Contain any third-party material including logos, drawings, tattoos, photographs, pictures, sculptures, paintings and other images or works of art, phrases, trademarks, trade secrets or other items without explicit prior written permission to use such materials.
  * Contain sexually explicit, graphic, gratuitous or unnecessarily violent content or defamatory or derogatory content against any ethnic, racial, gender, religious, sexual orientation, professional or age group or contain any pornographic or nude material.
  * Contain any private information about yourself or any other individual, including without limitation, information related to the health of the individual, financial information about the individual or any identification or account numbers related to the individual, with or without their permission or consent.
  * Contain any software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software, hardware or telecommunications equipment.
  * Contain any advertising, promotional materials, “junk mail,” “spam,” “chain letters,” or “pyramid schemes” or promote illegal activity or illegal contests, sweepstakes, or gambling, including any online casino, sports books, bingo, poker or any other form of solicitation.
  * Contain any material that, through any form of communication with the press, public, clients or media, disparages Tecademics or its employees, contractors, directors, instructors, owners, officers and creators, in any way. Forms of communication include but are not limited to social media websites, public forums, suppliers, vendors, clients, interviews, or recorded statements. You agree and understand that disparagement includes but is not limited to critiques, derogatory statements, ridicule, slander, jokes or insults at the expense of the company, management, senior personnel, independent contractors, products or services.
  * Anyone violating this prohibition will be subject to loss of position, title, status, benefits, wages, prestige, influence, and suspension, up to and including termination

We reserve the right to edit comments for content, remove off-topic contributions, delete offensive comments or remarks, block offensive contributors and delete actual or suspected spam content from any social media site. Please be aware that once you post something online, there is the potential for numerous individuals to read your words, even years from now. Therefore, we suggest that you exercise caution when posting on any social media sites and that you not disclose personally identifiable information such as your location, medical record number, personal medical information, financial information, etc. We are not responsible for the content of any comments or responses posted by others to any website or social media site, if any, managed or monitored by Tecademics. We do not control the placement of any marketing or advertising displayed on our pages by social media or third party organizations.

We reserve the right to respond to any post or user content and may occasionally, privately request your contact information to assist offline with your consent by routing the matter to the appropriate persons or department for further handling.

**QUESTIONS**

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to askmeanything@tecademics.com.
